bitterlawyer.com 2012-10-16

# Privacy Policy — Bitter Lawyer

### The Bitter Lawyer Privacy Policy

BitterLawyer.com, a service of Bitter Media, Inc. (“[Bitter Lawyer](http://www.bitterlawyer.com/ "Bitter Lawyer")”), supports the privacy of our readers. The following outlines our privacy and data protection policy.

Third-party sites you access via Bitter Lawyer are not subject to this privacy policy.

#### Collection and Use of User Details

When you register for any of our RSS feeds, email newsletters, or other subscriptions, we may collect personal details about you.

Personal information such as your name, address, and email address may be collected on our registration and order forms.

When you visit the site, we also collect web site usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer’s IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and, if you arrived at Bitter Lawyer via a link from another website, the URL of the linking page.

We use this information to:  
· personalize the content and advertising you will see based on your personal characteristics or preferences  
· notify you of relevant new products and features on Bitter Lawyer (if you opt in to receiving such information)  
· notify you of promotions from Bitter Lawyer (if you opt in to receiving such information)  
· ensure, as far as is practical, that our site is compatible with the browsers and operating systems used by most of our visitors

We also use the information for in-house research to:  
· improve our understanding of customer needs in developing Bitter Lawyer  
· build marketing profiles  
· aid strategic development  
· manage our relationship with advertisers

The results of all such research and analysis will be presented as anonymous or aggregated information and will not reveal any personal facts about individual readers.

#### User Choices

Registration and order forms may provide you with a series of choices regarding promotional activity and other forms of communication with you.

If you want to be kept informed of Bitter Lawyer products and offers, as well as technical or functional developments related to our website and online services, then you should select the relevant opt-in box.

#### Use of Cookies

A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user’s hard drive during a Bitter Lawyer visit. This file allows the user to move quickly and easily around our site. It is used to identify returning users and to identify subscribers. We also use a cookie to track a user’s sessions. We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so that we can develop Bitter Lawyer using analysis of people’s usage. We also use cookies and the information we collect to show you relevant content and advertising.

You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time.

Further information on the use of cookies can be found at:

http://www.cookiecentral.com.

#### Use of Email

Bitter Lawyer uses reputable third parties to deliver the emails you will receive from our site if you subscribe to our email newsletters or have chosen to receive information about Bitter Lawyer products and offers. These third parties use unique identifiers and invisible images (often called “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) to perform message open sensing, message format sensing, and clickthrough sensing on behalf of Bitter Lawyer in order to bring you more relevant information.

Content and some ad services in these emails are provided by Bitter Lawyer or a third party ad server.

#### Use of Advertising

We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit Bitter Lawyer. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to Bitter Lawyer in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

#### Use of Affiliate Marketing Programs

We occasionally link to product and service vendors using affiliate links. These affiliate programs may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit from Bitter Lawyer in order to track any sales or activities you perform on their site using a unique “cookie” on your browser.

#### Changes to This Statement

Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content on Bitter Lawyer we may make changes to our privacy policy and will reflect those changes in this statement, so you should check here from time to time.
